Guide to the Department of Astronomy, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records, 1860-1972; Accession 1977-A-001
  - VIII. Research Data, 1874-1962
    - Tables, miscellaneous and research notes
      - Occultations: Berlin, Strasbourg, 1927 (Box 129, Folder 182)
      - Occultations: Wilno, Lick Observatory, Pulhova, Els Fieth, London, 1927 (Box 129, Folder 183)
      - Occultations: South Hadley, MA, Charlottesville, VA, Tashkent, 1927 (Box 129, Folder 184)
      - Occultations, 1927 (Box 130, Folder 185)
      - Occultations, miscellaneous, 1929 (Box 130, Folder 186)
      - Occultations: South Hadley, Tashkent, Warsaw, 1929 (Box 130, Folder 187)
      - Occultations, 1928 (Box 130, Folder 188)
      - Occultations: Kiev, Florence, Berlin, Johannesburg, Pretoria, La Plata, Heidelberg, Breslaw, Padua, Strasborg, Jena, Warsaw, 1928 (Box 130, Folder 189)
      - Occultations: miscellaneous, Zo-Se, Omaha, Strasbourg, Lemberg, Berlin, Poughkeepsie Prague-Smikow, Lesshaft-Mirore-demi, 1929 (Box 130, Folder 190)
      - Occultations, 1930-1931 (Box 130, Folder 191-192)
      - Occultations, 1930-1932 (Box 131, Folder 193-194)
      - Occultations, 1928-1931 (Box 132, Folder 195-197)
      - The Bruce Photographic Telescope, 1896 (Box 132, Folder 198)
    - Correspondence: occultation, 1924-1925, 36-37 (Box 133, Folder 199-200)
    - List of Occultations, 1936-1937 (Box 133, Folder 201)
    - Material for Occultations: D. Brouwer, 1934 (Box 133, Folder 202)
    - Occultations of Stars by the moon Observed at Birmingham University, 1932 (Box 133, Folder 203)
    - Reduction of occultation Formula of Innes, 1932 (Box 133, Folder 204)
    - Alden, H.L., notes, 1929-1942 (Box 134, Folder 205-211)
    - Alden, H.L.: double stars, 1929-1942 (Box 135, Folder 213-216)
    - Analytical Solid Geometry, undated (Box 135, Folder 217)
    - Brown, E.W.
      - Analytical Statics, 1906, undated (Box 136, Folder 218-221)
      - Correspondence: Henry B. Hedrick, May Gunderson and others, 1908-1916 (Box 136, Folder 222-223)
      - Integral Calculus, report on, undated (Box 137, Folder 224)
      - Latitude
        - SD 2, undated (Box 137, Folder 225)
        - SD 2 1s, 1913 September 10-14 (Box 137, Folder 226)
        - SD 3 l = l' 2s, undated (Box 137, Folder 227)
        - SD 4 position or points, 1913 October 28 (Box 137, Folder 228)
        - SD 5, 1913 October 28-29 (Box 137, Folder 229)
        - SD 6 Pref. for points, 1913 October 29-30 (Box 137, Folder 230)
        - SD 7 Pref. for points, 1913 October 30-31 (Box 137, Folder 231)
        - SD 8, 1913 October 31 (Box 137, Folder 232)
        - SD 9 Pref for points, 1913 November 1 (Box 137, Folder 233)
        - SD 10 3 l - l Pref. for points, 1913 November 3 (Box 137, Folder 234)
        - SD 15 2F, 1913 November 3 (Box 137, Folder 235)
        - SD 16 Pref. for points, 1913 November 4 (Box 137, Folder 236)
        - Notes and tables, undated (Box 137, Folder 237-240)
        - Notes and tables, undated (Box 138, Folder 241-244)
      - Moon, table of ms., letters of computers, 1935 (Box 138, Folder 245)
      - Moon functions, 1906 (Box 138, Folder 246a)
      - National Research Council-National Academy of Sciences, 1923-1926 (Box 138, Folder 246-248)
      - Report and notes: Brown, E.W., undated (Box 139, Folder 249)
      - Research notes, 1916-1931 (Box 139, Folder 250-258)
      - Research notes, 1897-1904, undated (Box 140, Folder 259-264)
      - Rigid Dynamics, questions and examples in, undated (Box 140, Folder 265)
      - Sieve, 1899 (Box 140, Folder 266)
      - Theoretical Secular Acceleration with the Moon's Mean Motion: A report on an addition to, 1907 (Box 140, Folder 267)
    - Carinae F.V. by Harold Alden, 1938-1945 (Box 141, Folder 268)
    - S Columbae, 1928 (Box 141, Folder 269)
    - Comet Pareskevapoulos, 1941 (Box 141, Folder 270)
    - Conics, undated (Box 141, Folder 271)
    - Control, 1941-1942 (Box 141, Folder 272)
    - Differential Equations, undated (Box 141, Folder 273-274)
    - Differential and Integral, undated (Box 141, Folder 275)
    - Direct, undated (Box 141, Folder 276)
    - Eccentricity, undated (Box 141, Folder 277)
    - Eclipse: correspondence, notes, photographs, 1925 (Box 141, Folder 278)
    - Eros, 1930-1931 (Box 141, Folder 279)
    - Goch 8820, 1931-1940 (Box 141, Folder 280)
    - Heliometers
      - I: A report of the Reductions of the Observations for Determining the Scale Values of the Heliometers and of the Transit of Venus, 1882 (Box 142, Folder 281)
      - I: Scale Thermometer Readings and Report on the Reductions of 3, 17 and Tauri, 1882-1883 (Box 142, Folder 282)
      - I: The Transit of Venus and scale thermometer readings, 1882 (Box 142, Folder 283)
      - I: Heliometer Transit of Venus observations, 1882 (Box 142, Folder 284)
      - I: No. 5 to No. 9, 1882 (Box 142, Folder 285-289)
      - I: (printed) Instruction für die Heliometer - Beobachtungen Venus - Durchagänge, 1874, 1982 (Box 142, Folder 290)
      - Observations: Book 1-8, 1884-1886 (Box 142, Folder 291-297)
      - Observations: Book 9-14, 1886-1896 (Box 143, Folder 298-303)
      - Observations: Book 1-5, 1901-1907 (Box 143, Folder 304-308)
      - Observations: Book 6-10, M.F. Smith, 1907-1915 (Box 144, Folder 309-313)
      - Tables, undated (Box 144, Folder 314-317)
    - Investigative Method, undated (Box 145, Folder 318)
    - J.8. Terms factored by e', undated (Box 145, Folder 319)
    - J.8. Early work needed for theory and fundamentals, 1923 (Box 145, Folder 320)
    - J.8. Final approximation to Intermediate Orbit, 1929 (Box 145, Folder 321)
    - J.8. Paralletic Terms, 1939 (Box 145, Folder 322)
    - J.8. H sheets [symbol] Terms, 1929-1932 (Box 146, Folder 323-324)
    - Jupiter, 1927-1928 (Box 146, Folder 325-326)
    - Loomis
      - Book 1-2: Telescope, 1922-1925 (Box 147, Folder 327-328)
      - Book 3: Photo-electric, undated (Box 147, Folder 329)
      - Book 4-8: Photo Electric Photometry, 1933-1935 (Box 147, Folder 330-334)
      - Book 9-15: Photo Electric Photometry, 1935-1936 (Box 148, Folder 335)
      - Book 16-23: Photo Electric Photometry, 1937-1940 (Box 149, Folder 336-343)
      - Miscellaneous research notes, 1904-1947, undated (Box 150, Folder 344-351)
      - Newton, H.A.: research notes, undated (Box 151, Folder 352)
    - Notebooks
      - Division of Errors of Scale, 1887 (Box 151, Folder 353)
      - EandH Position Circle Sun Division Errors of Scales, 1886-1887 (Box 151, Folder 354)
      - 1 Observations on Saturn Asaph Hall, Jr., 1885 (Box 151, Folder 355)
      - 2 Observations on the Cygnus stars Asph Hall, Jr., 1885-1886 (Box 151, Folder 356)
      - 3 and 4 Asph Hall, Jr., 1886 (Box 151, Folder 357-358)
      - Chase, F.L.
        - 1C, 2C: Observations for Triangulation of Victoria Comparison Stars, 1890 (Box 151, Folder 359-360)
        - 3C.: Observations with Equatorial: Zona's Comet, asteroids and C and C, 1891 (Box 151, Folder 361)
        - 4C: Observations for Triangulation of Principal Stars in Conrae Berenices, 1891 (Box 151, Folder 362)
        - 5C, 6C, 1892-1893 (Box 152, Folder 363-364)
        - 7C: Observation of Stars with Large Proper Motions for Determination of Parallax, 1893 (Box 152, Folder 365)
        - 8C-14C, 1893-1904 (Box 152, Folder 366-372)
        - 15C-18C, 1907-1912 (Box 153, Folder 373-376)
        - 19C: XI Heliometer Observations: M.F. Smith and notebook for Collostat, 1912 (Box 153, Folder 377)
      - Miscellaneous, 1926-1956, undated (Box 153, Folder 378-382)
    - Observations, 1933, 1945-1946 (Box 154, Folder 383-383a)
    - Observations: University Observatory Oxford, 1888 (Box 154, Folder 384)
    - Oliver, C.P. and H.L. Alden: notes and papers, 1921, undated (Box 154, Folder 385)
    - Particle Dynamics: examples and theory, undated (Box 154, Folder 386-387)
    - P.E. data, undated (Box 154, Folder 388)
    - Photometer room, data for, undated (Box 154, Folder 389)
    - Printed material and research notes, 1926-1933 (Box 154, Folder 390)
    - Publications, miscellaneous, 1881-1939 (Box 154, Folder 391-395)
    - Publications, miscellaneous, 1845-1952 (Box 154a, Folder 395a)
    - Research notes, undated, 1924 (Box 155, Folder 396-402)
    - Rieffer clock No. 22- and 226, 1921-1945 (Box 156, Folder 403-404)
    - Rigid: Lecture samples and useless notes, undated (Box 156, Folder 405-406)
    - Saturn, 1926-1927 (Box 156, Folder 407-408)
    - Solar Eclipse (found among Ellsin Heliometers records), 1925 (Box 156, Folder 409)
    - Spectroscopic Binaries, 1940 (Box 156, Folder 410)
    - Tables of the Moon, undated (Box 156, Folder 411-413)
    - Tables of the Moon, undated (Box 157, Folder 414-416)
    - Tables of the Moon
      - Asteroid statistics, undated (Box 157, Folder 417)
      - Developments used in preparing manuscript for second part of theory, 1936-1937 (Box 157, Folder 418)
      - Distribution of perhelia and nodes, undated (Box 157, Folder 419)
      - Earlier developments and draft of parts of the theory: J.8., undated (Box 157, Folder 420)
    - Theory of Equations, undated (Box 157, Folder 421)
    - Thermometer calibrations, 1868-1943 (Box 157, Folder 422)
    - Voigthlander, Lunar eclipse, 1939-1941, 1949 (Box 157, Folder 423)
    - Young, A.S.: material used for revision, 1933 (Box 157, Folder 424)
    - Zeiss camera, 1938-1939 (Box 158, Folder 425)
    - Zenith tube: observatory, record book, 1915-1922 (Box 158, Folder 426-427)
    - Transit and clock observations. Yale University (Ledger), 1908-1913 (Box 159, Folder 428)
  - IX. Financial Records, 1882-1959
    - Ledger, 1882-1887 (Box 160, Folder 1)
    - Ledger, 1925-1930 (Box 160, Folder 1a)
    - Ledger, 1929-1961 (Box 160, Folder 2)
    - Ledger, 1933-1958 (Box 161, Folder 3-5)
    - Remittance slips, 1943-1959 (Box 162)
- Correspondence, 1848; Accession 1979-A-003
  - Smith, H. L., ALS to Francis Bradley re: claims made by E. P. Mason, 1848 February 14 (Box 1)
- Department of Astronomy records, 1873-1993; Accession 2008-A-128
  - Unmarked binder (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Parallaxes, 1976-1978 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Log, 1943-1957 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Property book, 1889-1926 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Bethany Dedication, etc, 1957-1958 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Bethany ano date 135 Prospect Street, 1950, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Yale Historical ano date Biographical, 1941-1970 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Gifts, 1950-1960 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Eros (Lano date-Rabe), 1952-1967 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Yale - Instruments, 1925-1950 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Loomis Project, 1914-1967 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - M. Ruddock - Clocks Waldo, 1875-1938 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence - Letters to South America -Gibson II, 1971-1975 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence -Letters to Hughes, Cesco, Samuels, Victoria ano date Gibson, 1966-1971 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - YC Correspono dateence, 1967-1973 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence from Gibson, 1970-1975 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Quality of plates consignments, Y-C, 1968-1970 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - El Leoncito Buildings, 1961-1962 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - I.A.U. Coll. 35, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Sydney Plates -Final, 1914 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Brouwer, 1920-1990 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Brouwer Bibliographies, 1943-1969 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence regarding Dirk Brouwer, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Sheffield Telescope, 1934-1983 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Winchester ano date observatory ano date heliometer, 1882-1933 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Before and After, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Photographs
    - Butler telescope, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Bethany Observation Station, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - 40-Inch Ritchey-Cretien type Reflector, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Catalogue Camera, 1954, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Hastings, C.S., 1916-1982 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Telescopes - Johannesburg, 1925, 1930-1934 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Measuring Instruments, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Yale ?, 1908 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - 135 Prospect Street, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Prospect ano date Canner Street Observatory, 1873-1955 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Radio Astronomy, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Reed Telescope, 1882 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Conn. Academy, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Jackson C. to DB, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Australia, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Index to Brouwer files relevant to Dorrit Hoffleit history, 1931-1932 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Bibliography, 1931-1932 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Program of the One Hundred-Eleventh meeting of the American Astronomical Society, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Brouwer Bibliographical, 1902-1966 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Correspondence Gold Medal RAS, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Brown, E.W., 1938 (Box 2, Folder 47 - 48)
  - Brown Funo date, undated (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Comparators, 1928-1934 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Elkin General file, 1887-1936 (Box 2)
  - Ford Foundation
    - Ford Foundation, 1960-1963 (Box 2, Folder 51 - 54)
    - Report, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - First Progress report, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - Seconod Progress report, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - Third Progress report, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - Recon Ins., 1964 (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - current, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - Fundraising and foundations, 1909-1957 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Graduate Students, 1923-1961 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - H, 1906-1923 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Hill, George William, 1899-1936 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Hill lectures, 1938-1942 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - D.B. to Cyril Jackson, 1964-1966 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Jackson, Cyril, 1964-1966 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Loan, 1932-1965 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Least Squares, 1922-1933 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - L, 1921 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Lunar Theory, undated (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - M, 1928 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Maps (foreign), 1911-1915 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Moon, undated (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - National Academy of Sciences, 1911-1915 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Newspaper clippings, etc, 1939-1967 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - O (obituaries), 1890-1974 (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Oort, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - P, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Photography, 1904-1937 (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - S, 1920-1923 (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - CD (?), undated (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - Frank Schlesinger bibliographical, 1871-1945 (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - Provost, 1962-1967 (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - Notes on Astronomy in Northern Hemisphere, 1751-1960 (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - Schlesinger, 1901-1943 (Box 3, Folder 86 - 87)
  - Division of Science, 1960-1962 (Box 3, Folder 88)
  - NSF Panel, 1952-1954 (Box 3, Folder 89)
  - Treasurer's statements, 1942-1955 (Box 3, Folder 90)
  - Advisory Committee of National Sciences, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 91)
  - International Astronomical Union on Sadler, etc, 1961-1962 (Box 3, Folder 92)
  - Argentina misc., 1956-1958 (Box 3, Folder 93)
  - NIF, 1954-1956 (Box 3, Folder 94)
  - NSF, 1956-1957 (Box 3, Folder 95)
  - Site survey, 1958-1959 (Box 3, Folder 96)
  - Plan for 20-inch So. Hemisphere, 1953-1956 (Box 3, Folder 97)
  - U.S. Naval Observatory, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 98)
  - Determinations of Periodic, Progressive, ano date Guiding Way Errors on the Mann Engine, 1965-1969 (Box 3)
  - 17" Measuring Engine, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 99)
  - Mann Engine Training and Special Purpose Notebook, 1967-1969 (Box 3, Folder 100)
  - Notebook, 1964-1972 (Box 3, Folder 101)
  - Procedure for determining engine errors, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 102)
  - Mann Engine errors, 1968-1972 (Box 3, Folder 103)
  - Machine errors, undated (Box 3, Folder 104)
  - Determinations of periodic, progressive and guiding way errors on the Gaertner machine, 1961-1963 (Box 3, Folder 105)
  - Engine corrections, 1933-1956 (Box 3, Folder 106)
  - Army Map Service -General reports, etc., 1962 (Box 3, Folder 107)
  - BPM catalogues, 1967-1969 (Box 3, Folder 108)
  - Solar reflex, undated (Box 3, Folder 109)
  - Status reports, 1962-1969 (Box 3, Folder 110)
  - Possible common proper motion stars in the South Polar Zone catalogue, undated (Box 3, Folder 111)
  - Army map service proposal, 1960-1963 (Box 3, Folder 112)
  - Zone 5, undated (Box 3, Folder 113)
  - Proposals Yale, 1969-1972 (Box 3, Folder 114)
  - Progress report, 1979-1982 (Box 3, Folder 115)
  - Available tapes, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 116)
  - Funo dates, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 117)
  - Measuring procedures for South Polar Cap, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 118)
  - Misc. folder, undated (Box 3, Folder 119)
  - C, 1925-1926 (Box 3, Folder 120)
  - D, 1922-1926 (Box 3, Folder 121)
  - Johannesburg, 1923-1924 (Box 3, Folder 122)
  - Latitude, 1924 (Box 4, Folder 123)
  - Moon Plate data, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 124)
  - South Pole, 1959-1968 (Box 4, Folder 125 - 126)
  - Measuring procedure, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 127)
  - Unnamed folder, 1968-1970 (Box 4, Folder 128)
  - Measurement changes: South Pole Cap, 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 129)
  - Mann Measuring Engine, undated (Box 4, Folder 130)
  - Measuring cards residuals for New Mann Engine, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 131)
  - Logs
    - D. Hoffleit Logs, 1959-1961 (Box 4, Folder 132 - 136)
    - Measuring Engine, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 137 - 141)
    - South Polar Cap, 1963-1967 (Box 4, Folder 142 - 151)
    - Misc Logs, 1955, 1961-1967 (Box 4, Folder 152 - 157)
    - Meteor Counts Plan A, 1934 (Box 5, Folder 158)
    - Meteor Counts Plan B, 1934` (Box 5, Folder 159)
    - Meteor Positions Asteroid Plates, undated (Box 5, Folder 160)
    - Zone -60 to -70, 1962-1963 (Box 5, Folder 161 - 167)
    - Zone -60 to -70 notes, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 168)
    - Sydney Plates -Replacements for Zone (Reg 33-34), 1962-1964 (Box 5, Folder 169)
    - South Polar Cap (books 11-19), 1968-1970 (Box 5, Folder 170 - 177)
    - Telescopic Meteors and photographic- AI, undated (Box 5, Folder 178)
    - Telescopic Meteors, undated (Box 5, Folder 179)
    - Mt. Tabor, undated (Box 5, Folder 180)
    - Lunar meteor observations, 1934 (Box 5, Folder 181)
    - Various observations, 1927-1931 (Box 5, Folder 182)
  - Photographs
    - Dick Brower, undated (Box 5, Folder 183)
    - Denison Olmsted, undated (Box 5, Folder 184)
    - William L.Elkin, undated (Box 5, Folder 185)
    - Fireball, 1893 (Box 5, Folder 186)
    - Unidentified photo, undated (Box 5, Folder 187)
    - One Hundreth-Eleventh Meeting of the American Astronomical Society, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 188)
  - Bethany Station (negatives), 1958 (Box 5, Folder 189)
  - Negatives of Yale Telescope Model
    - S.A. Telescope Model A, undated (Box 6)
    - S.A. Telescope Model B, undated (Box 6)
    - Yale Telescope Model C, undated (Box 6)
    - Group photographs (Box 7)
- Records, 1913-1931; Accession 2015-A-052
  - Catalogue of Parallaxes, 1924 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Observation books
    - Undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - 1913-1914 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - 1914 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - 1915-1923 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - 1916 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - 1921-1925 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      Scope and Contents
      Includes observations by Dorothy Cabot and correspondence from Frank Schlesinger to the Lick Observatory in San Jose, California.
    - 1922-1923 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - 1924 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      Includes historical data from 1915-1922
    - 1926-1930 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - 1928-1930 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - 1929-1931 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Records, 1967-1979; Accession 2019-A-0024
  Open for research.
  - 40 inch radio telescope logbooks
    - 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - 1969 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - 1968-1979 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 1 meter radio telescope observing books
    - 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - 1970 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Photographs of the radio telescope, Undated (Box 1, Folder 9)